Hi everyone! Today I come to my buddy's wild pond,
to catch some fish.
But his fish are not biting the hook.
Fortunately, I am coming with my draining machine.
I'm very ready to use it if I can't catch any fish.
Drain the pond!
His fish are very clever.
Enough!
It doesn't work at all.
Why is it switched off?
So the water is drained. Let's see if there are anything under the water.
Eh! Here's a,
"ji yu" (local carp)
I need some water.
We're taking the river snails as well.
The river snails...
Wa! Here,
here,
here is a fish,
and a river snail too.
This kind of river snails can also be taken.
This one, wa!
Wa! Wa! This is large enough.
This is, here's another one.
The whole family,
the whole family will go home with me.
The river snail...
Wa! Here,
here's one.
This is a carp.
Look! Here are so many river snails.
Look! These are the river snails picked by our younger brothers.
There should be,
around 2 kg.
All are large ones.
This is a small fish.
Here's a fish too.
Let me pour out the fish and have a look.
See how much we have today.
It should be almost two and a half kilogram.
Yup, two and a half, two and a half.
Alright!
The video ends here.
It's getting dark now. We need to head back as soon as possible.
They will be our dinner tonight.
There are still a lot of small fish down there.
Release the water back to the pond!
Let's put the rocks here.
Alright! Let's go!